creditsecret.org 2018-08-18

# Privacy Policy

**Last Updated** :

Info Up LLC (“Company,” or “We,” or “Us,” or “Our”) has created this privacy policy (the “Policy”) to explain our privacy practices so you will understand when and how personal information is collected, used, disclosed and protected with respect to this website (the “Site”). Individuals must be 18 years of age or older to use this Site and you warrant that you are 18 years of age or older.  By using the Site, you consent to the privacy practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us.  Therefore, you should carefully review this policy so you understand our privacy practices.

**Your information and how our Site makes use of it  
**  
Our Site may collect up to two kinds of information: personal (such as your name and    e-mail address) and aggregate information (such as the number of users who log on to the Site on a daily basis).  As a general policy, no personally identifiable information is automatically collected from your visit to our Site.  However, if you choose to participate in any promotional, e-commerce, or interactive activities offered on the Site, you may be asked to provide us with personally identifiable information about yourself (“PII”). When you set up an account on the Site, or purchase an item from the Site, we collect PII (which you provide) that may include your: (i) first and last name, age and gender; (ii) billing address; (iii) shipping address; (iv) other shipping addresses; (v) email address; (vi) phone number; (vii) credit card or PayPal account number; (viii) items purchased from us; and (ix) browsing and buying patterns.  You can change or update your PII on the Site by changing your account information.  The PII you submit will be used to carry out your requests, respond to your inquiries, and to notify you (if applicable) regarding any promotions.  Your PII may also be used by us and by carefully selected business partners, vendors and other third-party organizations (“Affiliated Third Parties”) to fulfill our services to you, to provide you with information about products, services and special offers we think may interest you, or to improve our products, services and advertising.

If for any reason you would no longer like to receive email and/or postal mail messages from us, you can [click here](https://nx300.infusionsoft.app/app/form/unsubscribe) to remove yourself from such communications. In addition, if you do not want us to share your personal information with Affiliated Third Parties, you can email us at [support@creditsecret.org](mailto:support@creditsecret.org) to remove yourself from such sharing. Please allow up to 10 days for us to process your request. However, please note that if you do not want us to share this information, we may be unable to fulfill your order or provide additional services.

From time to time, we may collect general statistical or aggregate information. Such information can include the type of browsers being used (e.g., Microsoft Edge®, Safari®, Firefox), the operating system you are using (e.g., Windows®, Android®, iOS® or Mac® OS), the number of users that visit a specific page on the Site and the nature and duration of such visits.  This information may be used to help analyze Site traffic and improve our services.  At no point, however, will the aggregated information personally identify you.

We reserve the right to disclose any personal or aggregate information if required to do so by law, including compliance with legal process served on Company, or if we believe that such action is necessary in order to (a) to protect or defend the legal rights or property of Company, the Site, or its users; or (b) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of the Site’s users or the general public.

You should refer to the rest of this Policy to see how we use, disclose and protect this information:

**Automatically Collected Information**

We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you visit the Site, our systems automatically collect your IP address and the type of browser you use. Static IP addresses are considered personal information. For mobile users accessing the Site, we automatically collect your Unique Device Identifier which is also considered personal information. However, the user cannot be recognized as a specific individual simply from a UDI or a Static IP address. Information may be automatically collected through the use of cookies or web beacons which are discussed in more detail below. We may also collect information about your browsing behavior, entry and exit points for the Site, search terms, website addresses you visit, page views, and impressions.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive by a website when you visit.  These files identify your computer and record your preferences and other data about your visit so that when you return to the site, the site knows who you are and can personalize your visit.  In general, we use cookies to collect information so that we can determine how to improve our sites by seeing which areas, features and products are most popular, to personalize the site and improve the site experience. Most browsers automatically accept cookies as the default setting.  You can modify the setting to reject cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit by editing browser options.  If you decide not to accept our cookies, you will still be able to access those parts of our site available to the general public but you may not be able to use some of the Site’s features or services and you may have a less satisfactory experience.

**Web Beacons**

Similar in function to Cookies, Web Beacons (also known as pixels) are small, transparent images that collect information such as the IP address of the requesting computer, the time for which the material was viewed, the type of web browser that retrieved the web beacon image, and the existence of cookies previously set by the Site’s server.

**Do Not Track Signals**

Some web browsers are developing or offering signals or other mechanisms for the expression of consumer choice regarding the collection of information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services (e.g., a “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) signal). A DNT signal is a HTTP header field indicating your preference regarding tracking or cross-site user tracking. We do not monitor or take any action with respect to DNT signals.

**Ads and Information About You**

We may work with third parties, such as network advertisers and ad exchanges, that use tracking technologies on our Websites in order to provide tailored advertisements on our behalf and/or on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet, and we may use third party analytics service providers to evaluate and provide us and/or third parties with information about the use of these ads on third party sites and viewing of ads and of our content. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements, which may be based on your activities (including past visits to our Websites) across the Internet and mobile media (“Behavioral Ads”). Behavioral Ads enable us to target advertisements to you for products and services in which we believe you might be interested. If you object to receiving Behavioral Ads from us on third party sites, you can learn more about your ability to limit Behavioral Ads below. Our third-party ad network and exchange providers, advertisers and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own technologies on your device and track certain behavioral usage information via a device identifier. These third-party technologies may be set to, among other things: (a) help deliver advertisements to you that you might be interested in; (b) prevent you from seeing the same advertisements; and (c) understand the usefulness of the advertisements that have been delivered to you.

Statements regarding our practices do not apply to the methods for collecting information used by these third parties or the use of the information that such third parties collect. We do, however, work with third parties to make efforts to have you provided with information on their practices and any available opportunity to exercise choice. We make no representations regarding the policies or practices of third party advertisers or advertising networks or exchanges or related third parties.

Further, while sites use a variety of companies to serve advertisements, you may wish to visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp), which provides information regarding this practice by Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including the “opt-out” procedures of NAI members. Opting out of one or more NAI members only means that those NAI members no longer will be allowed under their own rules to deliver Behavioral Ads to you, but does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different device or change web browsers, your NAI opt-out may not, or may no longer, be effective. You may also opt-out of receiving Behavioral Ads on participating sites and services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) website at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Similar limitations may apply to the DAA opt-out. We are not responsible for effectiveness of or compliance with any third party’s opt-out options or programs.

**Children’s Privacy Policy**

This website is intended for use by individuals who are 18 years of age or older.  Accordingly, Company does not knowingly, directly or passively collect information from individuals under the age of 18.  If we create offers and products that make it appropriate to collect information from individuals under the age of 18, we will notify you of the change in this Policy.

**Data Storage**

PII as well as aggregate information shared with our Authorized Third Parties may be stored on our internal equipment to which we allow access, or the data may reside on the external equipment of these third parties.

**Business Transfers**

Information about our users and the Site is one of our most important business assets. Therefore, information about our users, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger or acquisition, creation of a separate business to provide the Site or fulfill products, or the sale or pledge of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the Company.

**Security of PII**

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of PII in our custody and control. We also are committed to employing reasonable technology in order to protect the security of our Site. However, even with the best technology, no Site is 100% secure.  We will take reasonable measures which we believe are appropriate to protect your PII from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction, and, where possible, will ask that any third parties to whom we may transfer such information to take comparable steps to protect that security.

**Third Party Websites**

Please be aware that we provide links to third party websites from the Site as a service to our users and we are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those sites.  Please also note that these websites’ privacy policies will differ from those of Company.  Therefore, we encourage you to review and understand their privacy practices before providing them with information.

**Network and Information Security**

You should be aware that Company has no control over the security of other websites on the Internet that you might visit, interact with, or from which you buy products or services.

**Updating This Policy**

We may revise and update this Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new services or change existing ones.  Any changes will be posted to this document so that you will always know what information we gather and how we use it.  You are encouraged to print or download a copy of this document for your records.  If we make any material changes to our Policy or how we handle your personal information, we will post an “update” notice to our site and change the date of the Policy. If we are going to use any PII in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the change.  However, if users have opted out of all communication with the Site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner.  We will use information in accordance with the most current privacy policy.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Policy, please contact [support@creditsecret.org](mailto:support@creditsecret.org) – Or you can send us mail to: PO Box 29502 #58366 Las Vegas, NV 89126
